Justin Lacy

Game Developer

- Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Justin-Lacy/587b95166d51895b

Computer programmer with 15 years experience in Game Programming and online development, with a new focus on Mobile games and App programming.

15 years of professional Maintained, updated, and programming experience. debugged live code on popular Worked closely with artists and websites. writers to produce published Developed monthly feature games. releases and new game levels. Created back-end utility and Wrote code for database front-facing software. persistence and advertising Experience with mobile platform integration. development. Willing to relocate: Anywhere

WORK EXPERIENCE

Game Developer

Sandbox & Co - Boston, MA - November 2015 to February 2016

- Continued development of online and mobile game, Poptropica.
- Worked on Engine programming for new Unity conversion.

Computer Programmer

Pearson Education - Upper Saddle River, NJ - March 2009 to November 2015

- Programmed levels for Poptropica, a popular online children's game.
- Maintained and debugged live code.
- Worked with artists and writers at all stages of game design and production.
- Coded front-end of Poptropica Realms, a sandbox world within Poptropica.

Computer Programmer

Letterpress Software - North Logan, UT - May 2003 to June 2007

- Developed educational games and general educational software.
- Created engines for adventure games and interactive presentations.
- Translated and ported existing software to multiple languages/platforms.

EDUCATION

Computer Science and Mathematics

University of California - Davis, CA

LINKS

http://lerpinglemur.com

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

TECHNICAL SKILLS
Skills Proficiency Total Years Last Used
C#, Unity Development Advanced 10 2016
Actionscript, Flash Expert 15 2017
Development
Java, Android Programming Advanced 5 2014
HTML/css/javascript Intermediate 15 2017
/PHP/SQL